<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Time Warp Scan\: Body Scanner</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="horizontal">Horizontal</string>
    <string name="vertical">Vertical</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="select_all">Select All</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us</string>
    <string name="more_apps">More Apps</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_link">https://encoremediainc.blogspot.com/p/privacy-policy.html</string>
    <string name="privacypolicy">Posting rules you should be taking care of before you start interaction on our website/application:
    \n\nAssuring you carry the rights and eligibility to post any form of content you are about to share. We never permit nudism on application/website. We won\'t allow posting of sexually explicit content, sexually explicit text, images, or audio content depicting extreme sexual acts such as acts of posting Content that drives traffic to pornographic online services. Please note that we may make exceptions based on artistic, educational, historical, documentary, or scientific nature, or where there are other considerable benefits to the public at large.
    \n\nWe don\'t permit encouragement or applaud towards terrorism, formed crime scenes or hate association groups on our application/website. Attempting to sell sexual services or weapons and harmful drugs are also not permitted. We will remove reasonable threats of severity, hate arousing content/speech and the intentionally pointing of private individuals. We do not permit attacks/abuse based on skin colour, native, sex, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, religion, disability or disease.
    \n\nGraphic violence is not allowed and we may remove videos or images of intense, graphic violence to make sure our application/website stays appropriate for everyone.
        \n\nIf anyone or any account is spotted doing the above restricted activities they can be booked and arrested for the same. If viewers spot any violations of the above rules they have the right to report the content to us by using the report feature given in our application/ website.\n\n</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="actual_privacypolicy">This Privacy Policy explains how Drive2Media Global Advertising (referred to as \"We,\" \"Us,\" or \"Our\") safeguards your personal information when you use our Services (referred to as \"Services\"), which include the mobile phone applications (referred to as \"Mobile\").  \n\nPlease carefully read this privacy policy. By accessing or making use of the service, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions outlined in this document as well as any other terms and conditions referred to.  \n\nInformation, including personal information, collected while you use our services is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. For this Privacy Policy, \"personal information\" refers to information that enables us to personally identify you, either by itself or in conjunction with other data. \"Aggregate\" data, which we collect about the use of the Services or about a group or category of Services or users from which individual identities or other personal information have been removed, and \"personal information\" does not include technical, device, or usage information that cannot be used to identify you personally. We may share aggregate and non-personal information about our users with third parties for a variety of purposes, and this Privacy Policy does not restrict or limit our collection or use of such information.  \n\n<b>DEVICE PERMISSIONS</b>  \n\nandroid.permission.CAMERA \n\nandroid.hardware.CAMERA \n\nandroid.hardware.camera.FLASH \n\nandroid.permission.WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE \n\nandroid.permission.INTERNET \n\nandroid.permission.READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE \n\nandroid.permission.WRITE_SETTINGS  \n\n<b>TECHNICAL INFORMATION</b> \n\nWhen you use our website or mobile application, for example, certain network and internet activity data are automatically generated and logged. We collect the following types of technical data:  \n\nInformation from the log: We refer to this electronic record of your app usage as \"log data\" because our servers passively store it. We collect information about your interactions with our website, services, and content, such as your IP address, browser type and settings, the date and time of your visit, search terms, the most frequently used parts of our site and services, device data, and cookie data, among other things. We use log data to run our services, keep them secure, make sure they work reliably, and make your experience better.  \n\nWe automatically collect some information when you visit the Site. This kind of information can include your browser type, language, access time, and the website from which you linked to our site. We also get information about how you use the Site and what you do there, including the operating system of your computer.  \n\nCookies\' data. To run our services and collect log data, we make use of technologies like \"cookies.\" Click \"COOKIES\" below to learn more about how we use cookies.  \n\nDevice data. We combine and collect information about your device usage and activity, as well as the devices you use to access our apps and services.  \n\nInformation about images in metadata. We gather the metadata associated with your content. Your images, for instance, may be accompanied by additional content such as comments and a hashtag (for example, to mark keywords). This makes your content more interactive and searchable by others.  \n\nAll of this data is only used to improve the quality of our service. Information regarding the number of users of our Site or Mobile may occasionally be provided to the owners and operators of third-party websites and mobile applications that have a link to our site or application. None of this information can be used to locate you.  \n\n<b>SERVICE DATA</b>  \n\nYou must provide a photo before the photo editing event to use our services. The encrypted connection is used to send the photos to our servers, where the processing takes place and necessitates an Internet connection. To safeguard the confidentiality and integrity of the transmission process, we make use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.  \n\nThe original photos and results are automatically deleted from our servers two weeks after the last interaction for non-registered users and users who do not share their results in the Services. Unless a user either removes the images themselves or requests that the images be removed by contacting our support team, registered users who share their results within the Services that provide special social network features will have their shared content stored on the servers and displayed within the Services.  \n\nWe employ special face recognition technologies whenever you select an effect that involves manipulating the face;  \n\nrecognize a face in a picture;  \n\nlocate the necessary facial key points (the setting varies depending on the effect);  \n\nand incorporate the effect into your image.  \n\nWithin two weeks of the last interaction with the photo, both the photo that corresponds to the detected facial key points and the photo is removed from our providers\' servers. This is done to speed up any subsequent processing of the same picture.  \n\nUSE OF \"Cookies\" Certain information is automatically gathered by us. Locally stored cookies are little data files. For system administration and to report information to our branded partners, we use cookies to collect information about your device, including, where available, your IP address, operating system, and browser type.  \n\nWhen you visit the Site or use the Services, we may store some information locally. This information helps us remember your preferences and makes it easier for you to use the site or services. Other Site or Service features and features that recognize your account as logged in are provided by the information stored in a cookie. Cookies used by our advertisers or brand partners are beyond our control.  \n\n<b>SECURITY</b>  \n\nOur policies and the technology we employ are designed to prevent unauthorized access to and use of your personal information. As new technology becomes available, these measures will continue to be updated. However, we are unable to guarantee that outsiders will not be able to circumvent our security measures. It is your responsibility to safeguard your password when using our Services. Do not disclose it to anyone else. Please let us know right away if you think your account has been hacked or your password has been used improperly.  \n\n<b>CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY</b>  \n\nFrom time to time, we may modify this Privacy Policy. We will update this site with the most recent Privacy Policy if we make any changes to it that we believe will significantly affect your rights. When you use the Services, we recommend that you review this Privacy Policy to learn how your personal information is used.  \n\nQUESTIONS Please contact us at appblog66@gmail.com if you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="firebase_name">FaceWarpData</string>
</resources>